framedestination.com 2004-12-04

# Frame Destination Home

| 

### Frame Destination, Inc. Privacy Policy

Information that you provide to Frame Destination, Inc., is confidential.When you place a purchase, the check out is processed on secure servers. By viewing or using the Frame Destination Inc. website or related websites, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. Frame Destination, Inc. reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use. However, we do not intend to change the fundamental tenet of this policy -- your information will not be sold to anyone outside of Frame Destination, Inc. The information we collect is solely for the purpose of communicating with our customers. However, we must cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a user.

#### Collection of Personal Information

When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, Frame Destination, Inc. may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is optional for you to provide your information and engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Frame Destination, Inc. may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address and telephone numbers. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

#### Security

Please note that any area of our site that requires you to reveal financially sensitive information (ie, your Credit Card number) to continue with an activity -- such as an online purchase -- is located on a Secure Server(s).

#### Cookies

Some sections of our site utilize cookies as a convenience for our visitors. As an example \- whenever a visitor fills out an online form, we set a cookie, and if accepted, it will prevent the visitor from having to reenter their information for any other online form on the site. So if you provide your info on our Contact form, you will not be required to fill out the Online Video access form. However, you will be required to enter your information on our Order System as we need the most current information you can provide for order fulfillment. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. While Frame Destination, Inc. uses cookies to track your visit to our website, and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Frame Destination, Inc. with personal information.

#### Consistency

Please note that if you provide Frame Destination, Inc. with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that we may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that we may not), Frame Destination, Inc. cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored. Outside Sites, please note that Frame Destination, Inc. is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Frame Destination, Inc. websites to which this site or any other Frame Destination, Inc. website may link.

If you have further questions, please e-mail us at: [info@framedestination.com](mailto:info@framedestination.com)

|
